{
    "subject": "resource/Ysgol_John_Bright",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Wales",
    "human_readable": "Ysgol John Bright is located in Wales.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880824089050293,
            "question": "In which part of Wales is Ysgol John Bright situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9206487536430359,
            "question": "Where is Ysgol John Bright located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812483906745911,
            "question": "What country is Ysgol John Bright in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5105598568916321,
            "question": "What type of institution is Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49446600675582886,
            "question": "Is there anything notable about Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4260006546974182,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38538020849227905,
            "question": "How old is Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3748212158679962,
            "question": "Is Ysgol John Bright a school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2796308100223541,
            "question": "What is the educational level of Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2324676513671875,
            "question": "Are there any famous alumni from Ysgol John Bright?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ysgol John Bright is located in Wales.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9274_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the educational level of Ysgol John Bright?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9274_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ysgol John Bright a school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9274_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Ysgol John Bright?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9274_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9274_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context information mentions that \"Ysgol John Bright\" is a school situated in the heart of the North Wales resort town of Llandudno, and also states that it is located on Maesdu Road, Llandudno in Conwy County Borough, Wales. This supports the triple statement that Ysgol John Bright is located in Wales."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the statement \"Ysgol John Bright is located in Wales.\" Specifically, document paths `54.txt`, `18.txt`, `34.txt`, and `13.txt` mention that Ysgol John Bright is situated in Llandudno, which is a town in North Wales."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}